Hi everyone and welcome to the last video here on my channel for this year.
Happy Christmas! I even hung up my Christmas sock here and I'm going to show you a try-on video today
and yeah, it's going to be fun. The video is sponsored by AliExpress and I was able to shop in the AliExpress store called Nibba
and selected some different stuff mesh catsuit PVC dress and a nice wet look
dress so I hope you're going to enjoy this one first outfit a mesh catsuit
bodysuit and I love the design it looks so dynamic somehow and yeah also really
comfortable because it's so stretchy so this is size M for Asian sizes you have
to be a bit more careful and check the measurement charts I think S would have
fit as well but I'm always careful and have to say the length is really good
it's not too short also the arms are long and the legs are long so everything that I'm
looking for in a catsuit. So of course it's impossible to wear underwear
underneath it but the design covers all the important parts and yeah I think you
have to wear it on special occasions maybe because it's not your everyday outfit but it's fun
and I really like it. Okay so for the next outfit we have one two three four
five six outfits in total and for the next one I'm going with a wet look neck holder dress
and it fits as well with a very low back here
again the situation that you cannot really wear underwear with the mesh part and the open back
but it does fit and it does stay in place that's always a good thing to know and to be sure of
so you can move around and it's not going to reveal too much. So I quite like the
look and the material is really comfortable. It's not size adjustable here in the back
but I think it fits fine and it's a nice little party outfit dress. As always
please have a look in the description text for all the links and all the item.
I'll write everything down below. If you have any other questions, write a comment and I'll get back to you.
For the next outfit I'm going to try on the only colourful item I have. Green. It fits to the Christmas sock somehow.
and I'm really curious. They are gloves and it's green. It's green velvet and I feel so festive
with it. I kind of feel a bit like a Christmas tree. No, I don't know. I think I should have
taken a size smaller although on the product page it said when in doubt size up and
if it's okay I think a size smaller would have been better
and I don't know it's a funny look feel a bit like I am going to play a part in the sesame street
also with the gloves that are attached on the front but not on the back so there's gap here
but I can't really take them off I don't know if this is so thought through but yeah I was
kind of impressed by the product picture so I thought I'll add it to the selection here
but here's a bit of advice always scroll down in the product to see the original pieces because
the product pictures at the top are like more of a reference picture and yeah always scroll down
to see the real deal I do like the corset belt here I think it adds a lot to the overall outfit
although I am more happy with the two picks I showed you before. I think a size smaller would
have looked better but I don't know so let's move on to the next outfit.
All right a PVC dress. It's the only PVC item today and there are shoulder pads again as well
as with the green jumpsuit so maybe shoulder pads will have a comeback. Who knows? Also
a waterfall cut here in the front and rather close back this time. So I just added a little
choker to have something else here at the neck because there's a lot of free room. I
can imagine that a bigger necklace would also look good. And yeah, I think it's a cool basic
dress and it's shiny. I like the overall look of the dress with the shoulder pads and the cleavage
and stuff like that and it's not my usual style but I think it's cute.
Okay I have another jumpsuit also with a lot of mesh and I'm going to try this one on. I've not
done it so far so let's see. I'm really happy so far with the mesh jumpsuit
because this one fits as well. It's again a nice look with the mesh at this time
it's velvet in between. So today is the no underwear video. Anyway the arms are
enough the body part is a bit short but not too short so this is size M again
and I yeah S would be too small so I'm glad I took the size M I think I like
the first one better because the design was a bit more intricate and detailed
and this one is a bit plain in comparison even. The velvet is running down the
whole leg. So it's on the inside of the legs here but you don't feel it. Okay I
I think I have one piece left and it's a bodysuit. I just love it. I know it's not the most exciting item. It's just a bodysuit. But I think it's a great basic piece. I paired it with a fake leather pencil skirt.
And I think it looks great together. And it's really soft and fits really good and it's really comfortable. So yeah, I'm totally happy with it. Not for like a fancy whatever event but for everyday.
my favorites today first place the catsuit the first one right from the start because of the
cool design then second place this bodysuit because it's really cool and third place the
pvc dress maybe together with the wet look dress but i think i like the pvc dress a tad more
yeah so thanks again to Aliexpress for sponsoring this video and I'll see you
in three weeks because I'm going to have a break for two weeks so I'll be back at
the 16th of January here on YouTube of course on Patreon I'll be active during
that time and yeah in Germany I would say guten rutsch which means slide nicely into
the new year I hope you have a nice time during the holidays and I'll see you
next year bye